ibankmarkets.com 2015-03-17

# Privacy Policy | ibank

Privacy Policy

**ibankmarkets.com (IB Markets Ltd) Privacy Policy**

Whether you are a former or an existing client or just visiting our website, the privacy of our users is one of our main concerns. We are committed to safeguarding all personal information collected from our clients and visitors.

By providing ibankmarkets.com (IB Markets Ltd) with your personal information such as your Name, Mailing Address, ID number, Passport Number etc., you are providing us with full consent to gather, utilize, store and protect the information provided in the manner described below.

**When the Information is collected from our Clients?**

We will collect personal information from clients under the circumstances stated below:

  * When opening a Live/Demo account with ibankmarkets.com (IB Markets Ltd) (When filling in electronic registration forms)
  * When funding your personal trading account
  * When withdrawing from your personal trading account
  * The Personal Information that may be Collected Includes:
  * Personal Information such as Full Name, Address, Date of Birth, ID Number and Occupation
  * Financial Information such as assets, investment experience and monthly income, in order to evaluate your trading experience
  * When funding your account or withdrawing from your account, we may request documents such as a copy of an ID Document, Utility Bills and a Bank Statement

The above information collected from clients, help ibankmarkets.com (IB Markets Ltd) understand your financial needs, provide you with products and services suitable to your needs, process your account transactions in a timely manner as well as provide you with the highest level of customer support.

**How the information is collected from ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) Clients?**

Clients willingly provide ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) with the personal information collected under the following in the following ways:

  * On Completion of Electronic registration forms placed on the Ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) Website or on an ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) Minisite
  * When funding or withdrawing from trading accounts, clients voluntarily provide required documents
  * When trading on the Ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) system
  * When contacting Ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) or responding to a promotion advertised
  * There is certain information that is indirectly collected by Ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) such as: IP Address, operating system, software configuration and the use of cookies.

**What is the purpose of using the information collected by ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd)**

ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) will utilize the information collected from clients for the following purposes:

  * To verify clients identity
  * To set up, maintain and manage clients’ personal trading account
  * To process deposits and withdraws in clients’ personal trading account
  * To keep clients up to date with news, updates and new promotions at Ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd)
  * To analyze client activity in order to improve and provide clients with the best products and services.
  * To provide clients with top – quality customer support
  * The Sharing of Clients Personal Information

ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) does not share any client information with any affiliated or unaffiliated 3rd parties and only under the below circumstances will client’s personal information be shared:

In order to open, operate and serve your personal trading account, ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) may share information with service providers such as attorneys, accountants, auditors, and other financial professionals

In order to protect against fraud, money laundering, unauthorized transactions, claims or other liabilities

Income, credit history, net worth, or income information, will not be shared by ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) under no circumstances

The company may share information with affiliates and introducing brokers, mainly for the calculation of these entities’ compensation.

**How does ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) Protect the Information you Provide?**

  * Right on top of the ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) priority list is client’s security, therefore ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) takes all the necessary steps to make sure that your data is safe with us.
  * ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) uses the top notch data security technology, firewalls and data encryption.
  * Every client owns his own personal user name and password which he uses to access ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) systems.
  * All client information at ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) is restricted to a small group of management and employers that need to use this information

**Links found on the ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) Website**

Links to external sites may be found on the ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) website. ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) takes no responsibility for the content on the external websites and advices all clients to read the privacy policy of the external websites before leaving any personal information. The ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd).

**Questions, Concerns or Complaints?**

If you have any questions, concerns or complaints, please don’t hesitate to contact us via phone, email or chat. ibankmarkets.com (IB markets Ltd) offers customer support in multiple languages.
